[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Which web series features the character 'Eleven'?",
    "options": [
      "Dark",
      "The Umbrella Academy",
      "Stranger Things",
      "The OA"
    ],
    "answer": "Stranger Things"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "Which web series is based on the British royal family?",
    "options": [
      "The Crown",
      "Bridgerton",
      "Downton Abbey",
      "Victoria"
    ],
    "answer": "The Crown"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What is the name of the crime drama web series starring Bryan Cranston as a chemistry teacher?",
    "options": [
      "Breaking Bad",
      "Ozark",
      "Better Call Saul",
      "Narcos"
    ],
    "answer": "Breaking Bad"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Which web series is a prequel to 'Breaking Bad'?",
    "options": [
      "Better Call Saul",
      "El Camino",
      "Narcos",
      "The Wire"
    ],
    "answer": "Better Call Saul"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Which web series is based on a dystopian novel by Margaret Atwood?",
    "options": [
      "The Handmaid's Tale",
      "Black Mirror",
      "The Man in the High Castle",
      "Altered Carbon"
    ],
    "answer": "The Handmaid's Tale"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What is the name of the Spanish heist crime drama web series?",
    "options": [
      "Money Heist",
      "Narcos",
      "Elite",
      "Dark"
    ],
    "answer": "Money Heist"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Which Marvel web series follows the characters Wanda Maximoff and Vision?",
    "options": [
      "WandaVision",
      "Loki",
      "Hawkeye",
      "Moon Knight"
    ],
    "answer": "WandaVision"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Which web series is set in a theme park populated by android hosts?",
    "options": [
      "Black Mirror",
      "Westworld",
      "Raised by Wolves",
      "Altered Carbon"
    ],
    "answer": "Westworld"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What Netflix series follows the lives of a chess prodigy named Beth Harmon?",
    "options": [
      "The Queen's Gambit",
      "Mindhunter",
      "Unorthodox",
      "The Crown"
    ],
    "answer": "The Queen's Gambit"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Which sci-fi anthology series explores the dark side of technology?",
    "options": [
      "Black Mirror",
      "Love, Death & Robots",
      "Westworld",
      "Altered Carbon"
    ],
    "answer": "Black Mirror"
  }
]